Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Library Admin. Office - Acquisitions Department., 1958-1962.; 894329 (Box 89, Folder 10-12)
- American Library Association., 1960.; 894328 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of the Librarian to the Chancellor., 1954-1957; 894327 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Association of Research Libraries., 1962.; 894326 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of the Librarian., 1954/1955-1958/1959.; 894325; This folder not in box 2016 feb 17 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Branch Library monthly statistics., 1961/1962.; 894324 (Box 90, Folder 5-6)
- Budget requests - Berkeley, 1955/1956-1961/1962; 894323 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
- Budget requests - Santa Barbara, 1956-1964; 894322 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Budget requests - San Francisco Medical Center, 1953-1964; 894321 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Library Admin. Office - Capital Improvements, 1958-1961; 894320 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Catalog Department, 1954/1955-1963; 894319 (Box 92, Folder 1-4)
- Checking Procedures Committee, Final Report, 1955; 894318 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Library Admin. Office - Circulation Department., 1958-1960.; 894317 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Library Admin. Office - Circulation Department., 1960-1963.; 894316 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
- Classification Study., 1959-1963.; 894315 (Box 93, Folder 3-4)
- Departmental monthly statistics., 1961/1962.; 894314 (Box 93, Folder 5-6)
- University Research Library. Plans, Unit I. Now D9., 1964.; 894313 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Archer, H. Richard., 1954-1959; 1962-1965.; 894312 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Bennett, Fleming., 1952-1960.; 894311 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Non-Academic Library Restructure (working papers)., 1963-1965.; 894310 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Special Committee Investigating the Possibility of Establishing a National Film Archive on the UCLA Campus - report., 1958.; 894309 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Library Building Alterations - UCLA - Project No. 89450., 1949.; 894308 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Clark Library Alterations, Project No. 84510., 1950.; 894307 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- UC Santa Barbara Library Building., 1950.; 894306 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Branch Libraries - Annual reports and other major reports: Agriculture Library (annual report and Agriculture Library Committee Report)., 1959/1960.; 894305 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Art Library., 1959-1961.; 894304 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Biomedical Library., 1947/1948; 1953/1954; 1959-1961.; 894303 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Business Administration Library., 1959-1961.; 894302 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Chemistry Library., 1959-1961.; 894301 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Education Library., 1949-1954; 1959-1961.; 894300 (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
- Engineering and Mathematical Sciences Library., 1946 Jul-Dec; 1947 Jan-Jun; 1951-1953; 1959-1962.; 894299 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Geology-Geophysics Library., 1959-1961.; 894298 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Graduate Reading Room, Annual reports., 1936; 1948-1964.; 894297 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Home Economics Library., 1959/1960.; 894296 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Institute of Industrial Relations Library., 1959/1960.; 894295 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Music Library., 1959/1960.; 894294 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Oriental Library., 1959-1962.; 894293 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Physics Library., 1959-1961.; 894292 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Theater Arts Library., 1959/1960.; 894291 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- University Elementary School Library (Annual reports and report on the functions of the UES as a Laboratory School of the UCLA Department of Education...), 1951/1952; 1959-1961.; 894290 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Branch Libraries - Annual reports, etc.: William A. Clark Memorial Library., 1959/1960.; 894289 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Library departments - Annual reports, 1959-1962.; 894288; Includes Acquisitions, Catalog, Circulation, Oral History Program, (Box 97, Folder 2-9)
- Library departments - Annual Reports, 1959/1960-1961/1962.; 894284; Includes Reference, Serials and Special Collections (Box 98, Folder 1-3)
- Branch Libraries - monthly and quarterly reports, 1959-1961.; 894281; Includes Agriculture, Biomedical, Business Administration, Chemistry, Edcation, Engineering-Math Sciences, Geology, Graduate REading room, Home Economics, Institute of Industrial Relations, Music, Oriental and Physics Libraries (Box 98, Folder 4-17)
- Branch Libraries - monthly and quarterly reports., 1959-1961.; 894267; Includes University Elementary School and William Andrews Clark Libraries (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
- Library departments - monthly and quarterly reports:, 1959-1960.; 894264; Includes Circulation, and College Library (Box 99, Folder 3-6)
- Library departments - monthly and quarterly reports, c. 1959-1963; 894259; Includes Acquisitions, Catalog, Circulation, College Library, Reference, Serials and Special Collections departments. (Box 100, Folder 1-8)
- Branch Library monthly statistics., 1962/1963.; 894251 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Dickey, Donald., 1949/1953.; 894250 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Branch Librarians meetings., 1967.; 894249 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Librarians Office daily desk diaries., 1965.; 894248 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Lademann Report., 1967.; 894247 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Serials subscriptions., 1963.; 894246 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Acquisitions Department., 1962-1964.; 894245 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions - book budget., 1963-1964.; 894244 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Acquisitions Policy Committee., 1962.; 894243 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Annual report correspondence., 1959/1960; 1962/1964.; 894242 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Theses and Dissertations., 1959-1964.; 894241; University Archives (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Arrowhead Conference., 1963-1964.; 894240 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Art Library., 1958-1964.; 894239 (Box 102, Folder 7-9)
- Bacchus and Books, 1964; 894236 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Elmer Belt Library, 1943-1964; 894238 (Box 103, Folder 2-3)
- Bindery, 1955-1964; 894235 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Biomedical Library, 1963-1964; 894234 (Box 103, Folder 5-6)
- Index of Christian Art, 1963-1964; 894237 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Biomedical Library., 1964; 902981 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Book buying abroad., 1963-1964.; 894232 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Branch Libraries., 1958-1962.; 894231 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Branch Libraries proposed., 1956; 1959-1961.; 894230 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Business Administration Library., 1962; 1964.; 894229 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Campbell Book Contest., 1958-1964.; 894228 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Capital Improvements minor., 1962-1964.; 894227 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Catalog Department., 1948/1949; 1962 Apr-1965 May.; 894226 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Catalog Department - brieflisting., 1961-1964.; 894225 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Catalog Production Survey., 1959-1961.; 894224 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Chancellor's Office - admin. calendar., 1958-1964.; 894223 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Chancellor's Office Library Building Committee., 1958-1962.; 894222 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Chancellor's Office Planning Committee., 1960.; 894221 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Chancellor's Office Correspondence., 1958-1964.; 894220 (Box 105, Folder 5-8)
- Chancellor's Office Memos, 1958-1960; 1955.; 894219 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Chancellor's Office Memos., 1961-1964.; 894218 (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
- Chemistry Library., 1947-1957; 1959-1964.; 894217 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Circulation., 1962-1964.; 894216 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Citation indexing., 1964.; 894215 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- COMPS (compliments) (complaints)., 1964.; 894214 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Exhibits., 1958-1964.; 894213 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- English Reading Room., 1944; 1948; 1951; 1954; 1956; 1959; 1962.; 894212 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Engineering-Math Science Library., 1963-1964.; 894211 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Engineering-Math Science Library., 1962 Dec-1963 Jul.; 894210 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Education and Psychology Library., 1954; 1956-1964.; 894209 (Box 107, Folder 2-3)
- Farmington Plan., 1958; 1961-1964.; 894208 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Foreign Libraries Exchange Program., 1961-1964.; 894207 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Fry, George & Associates., 1964-1965.; 894206 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Geology Library., 1958-1964.; 894205 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Gifts and exchange., 1959-1964.; 894204 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Government and Public Affairs Reading Room., 1953; 1955; 1958; 1959-1964.; 894203 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Government Publications Room., 1963-1964.; 894202 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Graduate Committee for Library Affairs., 1961-1968.; 894201 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Graduate Reading Room., 1938-1962.; 894200 (Box 108, Folder 3-4)
- History of Science., 1964.; 894199 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Institute on Industrial Relations Library., 1952-1963.; 894198 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- InterLibrary loan., 1951-1964.; 894197 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Keys., 1948-1964.; 894196 (Box 108, Folder 8-9)
- Law Library., 1950; 1952; 1954/1955; 1957; 1959-1964.; 894195 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
- Library Administrative Office (Includes Calendar), 1955, 1958-1964; 894194 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Library Building Committee., 1963-1964.; 894193 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Library Building maintenance., 1964.; 894192 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Library Building maintenance - Receiving Room., 1964.; 894191 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Library Orientation Survey., 1961-1963; 1966.; 894190 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Library passes., 1960-1962.; 894189 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Library policy., 1964.; 894188 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Library privileges., 1961-1964.; 894187 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Library privileges - lending code rules., 1961-1964.; 894186 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Library privileges - lending code - card requests., 1958/1959; 1961/1962.; 894185 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Library privileges - lending code correspondence., 1958/1959; 1961/1962; 1964.; 894184 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Library privileges - lending code - revised., 1960.; 894183 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Memos to department heads., 1957-1964.; 894182 (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
- Map Library., 1957-1964.; 894181 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Memos from Chancellor Murphy and Assistant to the Chancellor Young, 1959-1964.; 894180 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Microfilm., 1955-1964.; 894176 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Music Library., 1958-1964.; 894179 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Music Library - Ethnomusicology Library., 1961-1963.; 894178 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Music Library - WPA Orchestral Score Transfer, 1963-1964.; 894177; Transfer of WPA transfer of orchestral scores and parts to the Los Angeles Public Library. (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Near Eastern Center., 1958-1964.; 894175 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Newspaper collection policy., 1947-1964.; 894174 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Oral History Program., 1958-1964.; 894173 (Box 111, Folder 7-8)
- Oral History Program., 1961-1962; 894172 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Oriental Library (East Asian Rudolph), 1956-1958; 1960-1964.; 894171 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Perishable paper., 1964.; 894170 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Photographic Service., 1940; 1944-1953; 1954-1958; 1959-1963; 1964.; 894169 (Box 112, Folder 4-7)
- Photographic Service - monthly reports., 1950-1956.; 894168 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Photographic Service., 1958-1963.; 894167 (Box 113, Folder 2-3)
- Policy on University Library diversification and specialization., 1962 Oct.; 894166 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Serials and periodicals., 1959-1964; 894165 (Box 113, Folder 5-6)
- Correspondence concerning Special Collections Acquisitions actual and possible - A-Z., 1960-1965.; 894164; Includes Haynes Foundation correspondence dating 1936-1962 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- URL (University Research Library) Move, 1961-1965; 894163 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Visitors - general correspondence, 1964; 894162 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Visitors - foreign: Asia - Yugoslavia, 1961-1966; 894161 (Box 115, Folder 3-20)
- Academic Communications Facility (Includes Audio Visual and Educational Television), 1954; 1960-1964; 894160 (Box 115, Folder 21-22)
- Academic Deans Council., 1961-1962.; 894158 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Administrators and Supervisors Association., 1963-1964.; 894157 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- African Studies., 1959-1964.; 894156 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Audio Visual., 1954-1963.; 894155 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Architects and Engineers., 1950; 1952-1958; 1960-1963.; 894154 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Book sale., 1962.; 894153 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Brain Research Institute., 1964.; 894152 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- (Daily) Bruin., 1949-1954; 1956; 1958/1959; 1961-1964.; 894151 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Chancellor's Office - correspondence., 1958-1961.; 894150; Includes budget correspondence (Box 117, Folder 5-6)
- College Library Building - Unit I., 1961-1964.; 894149 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- College Library Building - Unit II., 1963-1964.; 894148; Storage of Judaica and Turkish Collections (Box 117, Folder 8)
- College Library - Residence Halls Libraries., 1963-1964.; 894147 (Box 117, Folder 9)
- College Library Building - floor plans., 1963.; 894146 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- College Library Building - keys., 1963.; 894145 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- College Library Faculty Advisory Committee., 1956; 1961-1962.; 894144 (Box 117, Folder 12)
- College Library Building - equipment and furniture., 1961-1964.; 894143 (Box 117, Folder 13)
- College Library., 1956; 1958-1965.; 894142 (Box 118, Folder 1-2)
- Computing Facility., 1962-1963.; 894141 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Committee - Applications of Computer Facilities., 1964.; 894140 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Engineering and Math Sciences Library - retired files., 1958-1961.; 894139 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Engineering and Math Sciences Library Correspondence., 1962.; 894138 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Friends of the UCLA Library., 1951-1966.; 894137 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- Friends of the UCLA Library - publications., 1951-1966.; 894136 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Library Service, School of., 1961-1964.; 894135 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Mail room., 1964.; 894134 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Mathematics, Department of., 1960-1962.; 894133 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Nuclear Medicine Library., 1962.; 894132 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Numerical Analysis Research Library., 1960-1963.; 894131 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Photo reports., 1958-1964.; 894130 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Photographic policy., 1961-1962.; 894129 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Photographic policy - copyright., 1961-1963.; 894128 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs-Public Information Office, 1958-1964; 1307628 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Statewide - President's Office Memos and Correspondence., 1958-1964.; 894127 (Box 119, Folder unknown container)
- Branch Libraries monthly statistics., 1963-1965.; 894111; 2 folders Art, Biomedical, Business Administration, Chemistry, Education, Engineering & Math Sciences, Geology, Institute of Industrial Relations, Map, Music, Oriental, Physics, Theater Arts, University Elementary School (Box 120, Folder 1-14)
- Departmental monthly statistics, 1963/1965; 894098; 1 folders Acquisitions, Catalog, Circulation College Library, Photographic, Reference, Serials, Special Collections (Box 121, Box 122)
- Daily desk diaries., 1966-1971.; 894083 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  9 books
- Annual reports - Departmental and Branch Libraries., 1962-1966.; 894082; Acquisitions, Art, Biomedical Library, Business Administration, Catalog, Chemistry, Circulation, College, Education, English Reading Room, Geology and Geophysics, Institute of Industrial Relations, Law, Library Operations Survey, Map, Music, Oral History, Oriental Photographic, Physics, Reference, Serials, Theater Arts, University Elementary School and William Andrews Clark. (Box 124, Box 125, Box 126)
- American Library Association., 1953-1962; 1963; 1964.; 894056 (Box 127, Folder 1-3)
- American Library Association - Catalog Code Revision Catalog., 1960-1963.; 894055 (Box 127, Folder 4-5)
- American Council on Education - report on questionnaire., 1963-1964.; 894054 (Box 127, Folder 6)
- American Documentation Institute., 1961-1963.; 894053 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Association of College and Research Libraries., 1954-1957; 1961-1963.; 894052 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Association of Research Libraries., 1963-1964.; 894051 (Box 128, Folder 1-2)
- Bibliographical Society of America., 1961-1963.; 894050 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- California Librarian., 1950-1964.; 894049 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- California Library Association and Committees, 1964.; 894048 (Box 128, Folder 5-6)
- College, University and Research Libraries., 1964.; 894046 (Box 128, Folder 7-8)
- Council on Library Resources., 1963-1964.; 894044 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Librarians - merits and reclassification., 1963/1964-1964/1966.; 894043 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- Library staff list - confidential as of., 1967 Dec 01.; 894042 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- UCLA Library - budget., 1923-1945. 1950; 894041 (Box 129, Folder 1-4)
- UCLA Library - Budget., 1951/52 and 1952/53; 894040 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- UCLA Library - Branch Libraries Budget Proposals, 1963; 1307789 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- UCLA Library - History of the Catalog Department by Alice M. Humiston. 2 copies, 1919-1953; 894039 (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
  Contains two copies.
- Library of Living Journalism - correspondence., 1955-1966.; 894038 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Policy Committee (including material on LA Star)., 1958-1971; 894037 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- UCLA Librarians Association - pre-association correspondence and data., 1967.; 894036 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Unified Annual Report - size of the libraries of the University of California, Los Angeles., 1968 Jun.; 894035 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Library lending code., 1962 May 28.; 894034 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Size of the Libraries of University of California - tables., 1965 Jun 30; 1969 Jun 30.; 894033 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Statistics - UCLA staff., 1948-1966.; 894032 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Branch Libraries monthly statistics., 1965-1967.; 894031; Art, Bio-Medical, Business Administration, Williams Andrews Clark, Chemistry, Education/Psychology, Engineering & Math Sciences, Geology, Map, Music, Oriental, Photographic, Theater Arts, University Elementary School. (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Departmental monthly statistics, 1965/1967.; 894015; Acquisitions, Catalog, Circulation, College Library, Photographic, Reference, Serials, Special Collections, (Box 133, Box 134)
- Acquisitions and Book Budget and Book Funds., 1957-1962; 1965-1966.; 894000 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
- Bibliographers., 1966.; 893997 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Office of the Librarian - annual reports., 1965-1966.; 893996 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Office of the Librarian - annual correspondence report., 1964-1966.; 893995 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Architecture Library., 1965-1966.; 893994 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Architecture Library - Neutra Collection., 1961-1966.; 893993 (Box 135, Folder 8)
- Archives - thesis and dissertations., 1965-1966.; 893992 (Box 135, Folder 9)
- Arrowhead Conference., 1965-1966.; 893991 (Box 135, Folder 10)
- Art Library., 1961-1966.; 893990; Elmer Belt, Index of Christian Art, and visual aids (Box 136, Folder 1-4)
- Bacchus and books., 1965.; 893986 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Bindery., 1965-1966.; 893985 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- Biomedical Library., 1965-1966.; 893984 (Box 136, Folder 7-8)
- Book buying abroad., 1965-1966.; 893983 (Box 136, Folder 9)
- Branch librarians meetings., 1965-1966.; 893982 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- Branch Libraries., 1947; 1964-1966.; 893981 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- Business Administration Library., 1965-1966.; 893980 (Box 136, Folder 12)
- Business Administration Library - Robert Gross Collection., 1963-1966.; 893979 (Box 137, Folder 1-3)
- Capital Improvement - minor., 1965-1966.; 893978 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- Catalog Department., 1964-1966.; 893977 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- Catalog Department - brieflisting., 1965-1966.; 893976 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- Chemistry Library., 1965-1966.; 893975 (Box 137, Folder 7)
- Circulation., 1965-1966.; 893974 (Box 138, Folder 1-)
- Citation indexing., 1965.; 893973 (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Clark Library., 1961-1967.; 893972; Acquisitions Committee, Fellowships, Financial, and Seminars. (Box 138, Folder 4-10)
- College Library audio visual equipment and general correspondence., 1965-1966.; 893966 (Box 138, Folder 11-12)
- Hinman Collator., 1963; 1966.; 893964 (Box 138, Folder 13)
- College Library., 1965-1966.; 893963; Equipment and Furniture, Faculty Advisory Committee, Residence Halls Libraries, and Unit I and II (Box 139, Folder 1-6)
- Comps., 1965-1966.; 893957 (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Copyright., 1965.; 893956 (Box 139, Folder 8)
- Education and Psychology Library., 1964-1966.; 893955 (Box 139, Folder 9)
- Education and Psychology Library - clearinghouse., 1966.; 893954 (Box 139, Folder 10)
- Eng. Math. Library., 1962; 1965/1966.; 893953 (Box 139, Folder 11)
- English Reading Room., 1965/1966.; 893952 (Box 139, Folder 12)
- Foreign libraries exchange., 1965-1966.; 893951 (Box 139, Folder 13)
- Friends of the UCLA Library., 1965-1966.; 893950 (Box 139, Folder 14)
- Geology Library., 1965.; 893949 (Box 139, Folder 15)
- Gifts and exchange, 1959-1968.; 893947; Alexandre Rosenberg, Carroll Alcott Memorial Library Fund. (Box 139, Folder 16-19)
- Government Publications Service., 1964-1966.; 893944 (Box 140, Folder 1)
- India project., 1965-1966.; 893943 (Box 140, Folder 2)
- Insurance policy., 1959-1966.; 893942 (Box 140, Folder 3)
- Intercampus exchange., 1965-1966.; 893941 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- Keys., 1965-1966.; 893940 (Box 140, Folder 5)
- Law Library., 1960; 1965-1966.; 893939 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- Lending code., 1966.; 893938 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Librarians Conference., 1965/1966.; 893937 (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Library Administrative Office., 1965/1966.; 893936 (Box 140, Folder 9)
- Library Administrative Office - calendar., 1964/1965.; 893935 (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Library Administrative Office - receiving room., 1965-1966.; 893934 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- Library Committee., 1959-1966.; 893933 (Box 140, Folder 12-14)
- Library privileges., 1965-1966.; 893932 (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
- Library privileges publication programs., 1947-1966.; 893931 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- Library privileges systems automation., 1965-1966.; 893930 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- Library privileges staff - general., 1965-1966.; 893929 (Box 141, Folder 5)
- Maintenance libraries., 1965-1966.; 893928 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Manuscript Society meeting UCLA., 1964-1965.; 893927 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- Map Library., 1964-1965.; 893926 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- Math Graduate Reading Room., 1965-1966.; 893925 (Box 141, Folder 9)
- Memos - department heads., 1965.; 893924 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- Memos - to department heads and branch librarians., 1966.; 893923 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Memos - to staff., 1965-1966.; 893922 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Microfilm., 1965-1968.; 893921 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Music Library., 1965-1966.; 893920 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Oral history., 1965-1966.; 893919 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- Oral History Colloquium., 1966-1967.; 893918 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Oriental (East Asian) Library, 1965-1966.; 893917 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- Photographic., 1965-1966.; 893916 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- Photographic reports., 1965-1966.; 893915 (Box 142, Folder 9)
- Physics Library., 1965-1966.; 893914 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Printed book catalog - G.K. Hall., 1963-1966.; 893913 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Public law 480., 1962-1966.; 893912 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Public relations., 1965-1966.; 893911 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- Questionnaires., 1965-1966.; 893910 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Reference department., 1965-1966.; 893909 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Schedule of hours., 1965-1966.; 893908 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Schedules extended., 1965-1966.; 893907 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Security, Library., 1965-1966.; 893906 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Serials and periodicals., 1965-1967.; 893905 (Box 143, Folder 9-10)
- Space analysis., 1965.; 893904 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- Department of Special Collections., 1965-1966.; 893903 (Box 143, Folder 12)
- Department of Special Collections - Armenian Collection., 1960-1964; 1969.; 893902 (Box 143, Folder 13)
- Department of Special Collections - Benjamin Collection., 1962-1966.; 893901 (Box 143, Folder 14)
- Special Collections - Cummings Collection., 1963-1967.; 893900 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Special Collections - Huxley Collection., 1963-1965.; 893899 (Box 144, Folder 2)